# Stephan van Deventer

Full-Stack Developer me@polarizedions.net Robertson, ZA



ArchLinux
TailwindCSS Bootstrap
Scrum Git HTML5
PHPReact JWT
Nginx Javascript
EFCore Traefik Debian
IntelliJ-Rider Debian
Docker SCSS Slack
CSS3 DNS Python3
Typescript C#
Jira Portainer Jenkins
NodeJS GCP IntelliJ-Idea
Windows10 JavaVueJS
TypeORM MySQL
VSCode Bitbucket
Kanban Linux
jQueryGithub
SemanticUI



polarisa.dev



polarisa.dev/linkedin



polarisa.dev/cv



polarizedions.net

### About Me

I am a friendly, passionate, full stack developer from South Africa. Although my years in the workforce isn't that long, I have a lot of experience in many web-based technologies. I am always learning something new, working on one project or another. I am a fast learner, with great logic skills, and have a keen eye for design elements.

## Experience

WEBelievelT, Robertson — Fullstack Web Developer MARCH 2019 - PRESENT

- Contract work for The Delta Studios (thedelta.io), working on PRIV-IO
  - o Building with React to build a Digital Privacy Management tool
- Contract work for SQN (sqn.world), building front- and backend apps/systems
  - 3G platform stack: KnockoutJS, SemanticUI, VueJS, Javascript, Nginx, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, C#, Java, Python, jQuery, MySQL, git (bitbucket)
  - 5G platform stack: VueJS, Bootstrap, Typescript, NodeJS, Codefresh,
     Docker, Kubernetes (with helm charts), MySQL, git (bitbucket)
- Work on TimeTracker (timetracker.co.za), both front- and backend
  - Stack: C# (dotnet core), Dapper, Javascript, VueJS, SemanticUI, Jenkins (Declarative Pipeline), Docker, bash scripts, MySQL, git (bitbucket)
  - DevOps role to manage our internal infrastructure
  - Jenkins, Docker, NetData, Portainer, Traefik, Sonarqube Nexus, PiHole, Nginx, Linux (Debian)

Breededesign, Robertson — Intern JANUARY 2019 - APRIL 2019

- Internship, working on designing and building client websites.
  - o Using WordPress & Divi Theme, FTP, CSS, Photoshop

### Education

Robertson High School — Matric / NSC 2012 - 2016

- Passed IT in matric with 87% (classes at Worcester Gymnasium)
- Did well in other classes like Physical Sciences, Biology, English, and Math
- 73% Average in Matric
- Go-to backstage-helper & -coordinator for events, functions, and the School Revue

## **Awards**

- Runner-up for the South African Programing Olympiad 2016 (placed in the top 20 out of all participants in the country)
- Prize for top IT result in highschool for matric (87%)